<resources>
    <string name="app_name">About Me</string>
    <string name="name">Yusuf Abdul-Akeem</string>
    <string name="yellow_star">Yellow Star</string>
    <string name="bio"> \n Abdul-Akeem, also known as Hackmen right from age 16 is a Computer and Tech enthusiast,
            He was named and known for his passion for his curiosity about Tech. His hunger for
            knowledge and Curiosity of how things work being a fan of Aaron Swartz has led him to study
            Computer Engineering upon completing his senior secondary education and further enrolling as a
            CS student in the premier University of Nigeria, University of Ibadan.
        \n\n
            Being raised up by his mother who was a typist right from time, Akeem has influenced his
            mothers\'s career by enlightening her about today\'s\' Tech thereby bringing her business to a new
            level with various Tech optimisations as a result of is passion for exploring and experiment
            Tech gadgets hence creating a new standard for rivals and competitors.
        \n\n
            He is also known for his willingness to help people of different nature troubleshoot their
            hardware and software problems, people find comfort in consulting him for different scenarios,
            be it starting a software development journey, troubleshoot bugs in codes, reverse engineering
            integrated circuits/embedded chips seeking his expertise or experience regarding setting up or
            configuring various types of hardware, breaking down problems into smaller pieces (learning his
            approach to solving technical problems), just to name a few.
        \n\n
            He is currently learning Mobile Development (both Android and iOS) as he wishes to settle for
            Mobile Developer role at the present moment but aspires to become a Site Reliability Engineer /
            Infrastructure Engineer in the nearest future. He believes he has all it takes to achieve his desire
            and he won\'t stop until he finally makes his Momma proud, May God make his journey a successful one.
        \n\n
    </string>
</resources>